BU Records: Continuing Education, Inclusive: 1978-2005, undated, Bulk: 1992-2005, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
BU Records: Continuing Education
Inclusive: 1978-2005, undated, Bulk: 1992-2005, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
BU/356
Baylor University Continuing Education Office
14 document boxes
BU Records: Continuing Education contains a wide variety of documents related to the operation of Baylor Continuing Education program from the late 1970s up to 2005, including correspondence, memos, annual reports, course materials, grant and scholarship applications, financial documents, and other administrative files.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
In the 1970s, Baylor created the Division of Continuing Education in order to offer night classes and degree programs for nontraditional students.
In 1980, Dr. William Cooper was appointed Dean of Continuing Education. Under his leadership, Continuing Education focused on four areas: providing assistance to Baylor faculty in order to strengthen their teaching skills and research opportunities, providing training for Baylor staff to strengthen their professional skills, offering non-credit courses to address the needs of the Waco community, and coordinating summer session activities such as summer abroad programs.
In 1987, Dr. Robert T. Miller became Dean of Continuing Education. After his retirement in 1990, Annette Lindsey was appointed Director of Continuing Education. During the 1990s, faculty development and staff development were separated from the Continuing Education program, prompting a transition to focusing exclusively on education for the Waco community. As part of this transition, Continuing Education began several programs for specialized audience, including the Advanced Placement Institute for Teachers, the Baylor Institute for Learning in Retirement, and the Certificate Program in Nonprofit Management. The Nonprofit Management program began with a satellite coursed offered in partnership with PBS and the Learning Institute in 1998 before transitioning to offering classes led by local experts in 1999.
In 2005, the Continuing Education program closed. Baylor Learning in Retirement (renamed Lifelong Learning) moved to the Baylor Alumni association until 2013.
In 2016, Baylor Continuing Education was revived and began offering classes again in the spring of 2017.
Scope and Content
BU Records: Continuing Education consists of materials from 1978-2005, with some undated items. The documents reflect the operations of the Continuing Education office both in faculty development and in offering noncredit educational programs for the Waco community.
Series I, Administrative Files, is the largest series and contain the widest variety of materials. The series includes correspondence, memos, annual reports, minutes, course materials, grant applications, financial documents, legal agreements, travel itineraries, publicity, publications, and other documents related to Continuing Education. Series II, Nonprofit Education, contains materials related to the Certificate in Nonprofit Management program, including course materials, scholarship applications, correspondence, enrollment records, and financial documents. Series III, Course Catalogues, contains the catalogs advertising Continuing Educations course offerings for each semester.
Arrangement
The collection received an initial inventory in 2017 and was placed in legal-sized document boxes. The folders were in original order. Some intentional arrangement was evident. Folders on similar topics or of similar types tended to be grouped together in reverse chronological order. Labelled dividers also were placed in front of some groups of folders announcing their topic. Although this arrangement was obvious in some places, other parts of the collection had no clear arrangement and there seemed to be no clear overall arrangement of the folders.
BU Records: Continuing Education currently contains three series: I. Administrative Files, II. Nonprofit Education, and III. Course Catalogs. Materials related to the Nonprofit Management Certificate program and Course catalogs were separated to create their own series. The remainder of the materials were arranged chronologically and by topic. The original folder titles were retained, and items within folders remain in their original order.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. BU/356. Acquired 0-00-00
Related Resources
Items in related collections
William F. Cooper
Related references
“History.” Baylor Continuing Education. Accessed 2020 November 10.
Index Terms
Subjects (Organizations)
Baylor University.
Subjects
Continuing education.; Education, Higher -- Texas -- Waco.; Nonprofit organizations.
Genres
Correspondence.; Course catalogs.; Course materials.; Financial records.; Legal documents.; Minutes (Records)
- Administrative Files, 1978-2005; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  Series I, Administrative Files, includes correspondence, memos, annual reports, minutes, course materials, grant applications, financial documents, legal agreements, travel itineraries, publicity, publications, and other documents related to Continuing Education. The series is in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Postcards
  - History-Baylor Continuing Education, 1978 February 15-2002 September 10, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports (1 of 2), 1994-2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports (2 of 2), 1980-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - National University Extension AssociationDLOriginal Membership 1980, 1979-1980 June 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - National University Continuing Education Membership Dues, 1983 May 17-2002 July 9 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - National University Continuing Education Association, 1989 November 15-2003 March 29, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - National University Continuing Education AssociationDLGuidelines for Assessment and Evaluation, 1990 July-October 23 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Continuing Education (General File), 1983 March (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Community Assessment Program, 1983 September 15-1984 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Programs, 1984 February-2002 November 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Focus Group Report to the Dean of Continuing Education, 1985 January (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Community Assessment Program: Policy Report, 1985 May (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Community Assessment Program: Technical Report, 1985 May (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Self-Study University 1985 Faculty Development, circa 1985, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Staff Lunch 1986-Present, 1986 March 18-2004 October 27 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Waco Jazz Orchestra (1 of 2), 1986 May 5-1994 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Waco Jazz Orchestra (2 of 2), 1986 January 22-1991 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Pricing and Statistics, 1987-2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - SternbergDLReflections on the Arts, 1987 June 24-1991 Fall, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - President ReynoldsDLReports to, 1988 September 7-1989 May 18 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Development Committee Meetings February 1990-December 1995 (1 of 3), 1988 September-1997, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Development Committee Meetings February 1990-December 1995 (2 of 3), 1992 June-1994 September 22 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Development Committee Meetings February 1990-December 1995 (3 of 3), 1990 February 19-1992 October 26 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Development Grant Information, 1988 September 7-1993 December 1, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Grant List, 1990 January-1995 March (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Development Grant Information, 1990 January-1996 September 16, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Grant Copies, 1990 January-1997 May 12 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Instructional Development Grants 1996-1997 (1 of 8), 1997 February 16-March 10 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Instructional Development Grants 1996-1997 (2 of 8), 1996 October 1-1997 April 22 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Instructional Development Grants 1996-1997 (3 of 8), 1997 January 14-August 7 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Instructional Development Grants 1996-1997 (4 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Instructional Development Grants 1996-1997 (5 of 8), 1994-1997 February 10 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Instructional Development Grants 1996-1997 (6 of 8), 1996 September 17-October 21 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Instructional Development Grants 1996-1997 (7 of 8), 1996 August 8-November 11 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Instructional Development Grants 1996-1997 (8 of 8), 1996 May 28-September 10 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Discussion Group Harrington House 1992-1993, 1993 January 27-1993 January 20, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Enrichment InstituteDLSummer (1993), 1993 October 27-1994 March (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - New Faculty Orientation 1994, 1993 Fall-1995 August 31 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - New Faculty Orientation 1995, 1995 July 27-August 24 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Faculty/Staff ProgramsDLMiscellaneous, 1996 January 16-February 21 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Continuing Liberal Education in a Multicultural World Conference Program, 1989 February 15-19 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Publicity, 1989 September 14-1996 August 20 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Off-Campus Sites: Weeknight Seminars, 1989 October 11-1993 July 30 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Expanding Access to Knowledge: Continuing Higher Education, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - A Handbook for Professional Development in Continuing Higher Education, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Breakfast at Baylor with Alumni Association, 1991 February 28-2005 April 26, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Options, 1991 June-1997 April 30 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Continuing Education Advisory Committee (1 of 2), 1998 February 10-2004 September 28, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Continuing Education Advisory Committee (2 of 2), 1991 October 18-1997 October 23, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Marketing (1 of 3), 2000 Summer-2004 April, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Marketing (2 of 3), Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Marketing (3 of 3), 1992 Spring-2004 September, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Family Conference 3-24-1993 (1 of 3), 1992 March 5-1993 March 24 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Family Conference 3-24-1993 (2 of 3), 1992 Fall-1993 April 1, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Family Conference 3-24-1993 (3 of 3), 1992 March 24-1993 April 14, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Dean’s Review 1993-1996, 1992 November 17-1996 May 21 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Dean’s Review 1996-1997, 1996 July 23-1997 June 17 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Dean’s Review 1997-1998, 1997 May 13-1998 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Dean’s Review 1998-1999, 1998 June 26-1999 September 20 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Dean’s Review 1999-2000, 1999 September 21-2000 June 20 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Dean’s Review 2000-2001, 2000 September 19-2001 June 19 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Dean’s Review 2001-2002, 2001 September 18-2002 June 18 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Dean’s Review 2002-2003, 2002 September 17-2003 June 17 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Dean’s Review 2003-2004, 2003 September 16-2004 June 15 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Dean’s Review 2004-2005, 2004 September 21-2005 May 17 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Continuing Education Reviews: Principles, Practices and Strategies, 1993 January (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Continuing Education Opportunities on Campus, 1993 February 16 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Liberal Arts, 1993 November-1997 July, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Great Decisions 1993, 1993 January 27-October (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Great Decisions General Information, 1993 October-2004 May 23 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Great Decisions 1994, 1994 January 18-November (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Great Decisions 1995, 1995-1996 April (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Great Decisions 1996, 1996 February 1-March 28 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Great Decisions 1997, 1997 February 27 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Great Decisions 1998, 1998 February 25-April 17 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Great Decisions 1999, 1999 February 4-March 25 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Great Decisions 2000, 2000 February 3-April 6 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Great Decisions 2001, 2001 January 1-May 31 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Great Decisions 2002, 2002 February 7-April11 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Great Decisions 2003, 2003 February 6-April 3 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Great Decisions 2004, 2004 February 5-April 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Great Decisions 2005, 2005 January 27-March 24 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Women’s Issues Group February 1995-August 1999, 1994 March 4-1999 August 27 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - EvaluationsDLSamples, 1994-1998 June 26, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - North American Free Trade Agreement Conference 11-11-1994, 1994 October 13-November 12, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - International Women’s Conference 1995 (1 of 2), 1995 August 16-September 13, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - International Women’s Conference 1995 (2 of 2), 1995 January 12-September 12, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Driekant Northwest Europe 1996, 1996 January 1-August 15, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - France 1997 Europe Trip Information (1 of 2), 1996 April 25-1997 December 15 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - France 1997 Europe Trip Information (2 of 2), 1997 May 14-19 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - ItalyDL2000, 1997 October 12-2000 April 15, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Oxford, 1998 March 16-October (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - EnglandDL1999, 1998 April-1999 July 27, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Scotland and Ireland May 2001, 2000 May 16-2001 June 5, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Cancelled International Travel, 2002 February 15-2003 May 26 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - “In Focus” Newsletter National University Continuing Education Association, 1996 August 25-2005 April (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Strategic Planning Process August 1999-2002, 1997 April 16-2002 January 9 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Continuing Education, 1997 May 10-2005 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - LinkageDLGeneral Information, 1997 August 5-2002 January 1, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Linkage Agreements, 1998 April 21-2001 October 17 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Baylor University Market Assessment Report July 1998 (1 of 3), 1998 July 17-November 19 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Baylor University Market Assessment Report July 1998 (2 of 3), 1998 July 17 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Baylor University Market Assessment Report July 1998 (3 of 3), 1998 July 17 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - LinkageDLDallas Reports, 1998 December 1-2001 April 4 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Linkage Financial, 1999 January 30-2002 January 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - LinkageDLHouston Reports, 1999 September-2003 August 21, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Baylor UniversityDLHouston Client/Server Training Market Assessment Program (1 of 3), 1999 January (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Baylor UniversityDLHouston Client/Server Training Market Assessment Program (2 of 3), 1999 January (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Baylor University Houston Client/Server Training Market Assessment Program (3 of 3), 1999 January (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - LinkageDLInformation for General Council, 2000 April 8-2002 October 23 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - LinkageDLWeb Developer Certificate Program (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - LinkageDLWeb Developer Certificate Program (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - LinkageDLPublicity, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Continuing Education Telephone Survey, 1997 November (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Community Surveys, 1997, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Board, 1998 February 2-2003 November 4, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - University Continuing Education Association Executive Assembly September 1999, 1999 September 10, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - University Continuing Education Association Executive Assembly 2000, 2000 September 14-15, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Baylor University’s Technology Training Programs, 1999 September 21 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - High Technologies Course Catalog, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - The IT Job Seekers Handbook, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Southern History Boles Cherry Professor Winter/Spring 2000, 1999 October 22-2000 May 5, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Riding the Waves: University Continuing Education Association 85th Annual Conference, 2000 April 16-19 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Continuing Education in Market Place Deans and Directors, 4-15-2000, San Diego, 2000 April 18, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 2012 Vision 10 Year Plan, 2000 October 5-2002 March 28, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - University Continuing Education Associations Deans and Directors Institute, 2001 April 5, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - The Spirit of Enterprise: University Continuing Education Association 86th Annual Conference, 2001 April 507 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - University Continuing Education Association Commission Issue Papers, 2001 April (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Learning Resources Network, 2001 September 9-2002 January 21 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - University Continuing Education Association Region III Conference, 2001 September 23-25 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - New Designs for Learning: University Continuing Education Association 87th Annual Conference, 2002 April 17-19 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - University Continuing Education Association Commission Issue Papers, 2002 April (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Pathways to Success Conference Program, 2002 November 2-6 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - University Continuing Education Awards: Call for Entries, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Association for Continuing Higher Education, 2003 March 18-2004 April 20 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - The Next University: University Continuing Education Association 88th Annual Conference, 2003 March 28-30 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Focus Groups 2003, 2004 July 24-December 4, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Stored Files, 2003 October (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Center for Community Research and Development, 2003 November (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Twenty-fifth Anniversary Planned Celebration, 2004 March 3-2005 April 7, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - The New Majority: University Continuing Education Association’s 89th Annual Conference, 2004 April 14-17 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Baptist Laity Institute, 2004 May 20-2005 January 13 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Who’s Who in College and University Continuing and Professional Education, 2004 July (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Perspectives of the Past 25 YearsDLLecture Series, 2004 September 14-2005 May 11, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Department Analysis December 2004, 2004 November 18-December 21, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Texas Association for Community Service and Continuing Education, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and School Review 2005, 2005 January 31-February 28, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Revolutionary Times: University Continuing Education’s 90th Annual Conference, 2005 March 30-April 2 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Nonprofit Education, 1983-2005; 2
  Series II, Nonprofit Education, contains materials related to the Certificate in Nonprofit Management program, including course materials, scholarship applications, correspondence, enrollment records, and financial documents. The series is in good condition.
  Compact disk (CD)
  - Nonprofit World CDs and Information (1 of 2), 1983-1996 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Nonprofit World CDs and Information (2 of 2), 1998 February 11-June 3, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Nonprofit Management Mailing Lists, 1998 January 20-1999 September 1, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Attendance Records Telecast 1998-1999 (1 of 2), 1998 June 11-1999 October 26 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Attendance Records Telecast 1998-1999 (2 of 2), 1983 May-1998 December 8, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Rapoport Foundation, 1998 July 23-2003 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Nonprofit Scholarship Form and Memo, 1998 August 18-1999 June 17 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Scholarships Telecourse Nonprofit, 1998 August 27-1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Scholarship Information, 1998 September 9-2004 Fall, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Excellence in Nonprofit Leadership and Management 1998-1999 Certificate Program (1 of 5), 1998 September 17-1999 May 20 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Excellence in Nonprofit Leadership and Management 1998-1999 Certificate Program (2 of 5), 1998 October 15-November 19 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Excellence in Nonprofit Leadership and Management 1998-1999 Certificate Program (3 of 5), 1999 January 21-February 18 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Excellence in Nonprofit Leadership and Management 1998-1999 Certificate Program (4 of 5), 1999 March 18-April 15 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Excellence in Nonprofit Leadership and Management 1998-1999 Certificate Program (5 of 5), 1999 May 19-20, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Nonprofit Courses, 1998 September 11-2005 April 14 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Nonprofit Registrations Fall 1998-Summer 2000, 1998 September 17-2000 Summer (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Scholarship Summaries Fall 1998-Summer 1999, 1998 September 17-1999 August 12, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Scholarship Applications with ReportsDLSpring 2000, 1999 August-2000 July 11 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Scholarship Summaries Fall 1999-Summer 2000, 2000 January 3-August 9 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Scholarship Summaries Fall 2000-Summer 2001, 2000 Summer-2001 November 27, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Nonprofit Fall 2001 Scholarship, 2001 August 27-September 13 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Scholarship Summaries Fall 2001-Summer 2002, 2001 October 1-2002 July 26 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Scholarship 2002 Applications and Summaries (1 of 3), 2001 December 20-2002 July 2 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Scholarship 2002 Applications and Summaries (2 of 3), 1999 January-2003 February 5 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Scholarship 2002 Applications and Summaries (3 of 3), 2002 June 5-September 18 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Nonprofit Scholarship 2003 (1 of 4), 2003 January 10-November 21 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Nonprofit Scholarship 2003 (2 of 4), 2003 January 28-September 12 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Nonprofit Scholarship 2003 (3 of 4), 2003 January 9-February 5 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Nonprofit Scholarship 2003 (4 of 4), 1999 January-2003 February 20 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Nonprofit Scholarship 2004, 2004 January 27-2005 January 7 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Scholarships 2004-2005, 2004 June 15-September 15 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Nonprofit Winter/Spring 1999, 1998 October 29-1999 April 8, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Nonprofit Summer 1999, 1999 July 1-15 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Nonprofit Fall 1999, 1999 September 23-October 26, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Nonprofit Winter/Spring 2000, 1999 August 27-2000 April 11, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Nonprofit Summer 2000, 2000 July 10-27, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Nonprofit Fall 2000, 2000 September 26-2005 May 12 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Nonprofit Winter/Spring 2001 (1 of 2), 2001 January 12-May 16 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Nonprofit Winter/Spring 2001 (2 of 2), 2000 October 1-2001 May 11, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Nonprofit Summer 2001 (1 of 3), 2001 June 2-July 17 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Nonprofit Summer 2001 (2 of 3), 1998-2001 July 23, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Nonprofit Summer 2001 (3 of 3), 2001 January 4-September 10, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Nonprofit Fall 2001, 2001 September 10-November 19 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Nonprofit Winter/Spring 2002 (1 of 2), 2001 November 13-2002 April 25 (Box 12, Folder 2)